<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Manureva]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Manureva]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/manureva/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 06:37:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/manureva/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Set in one of the world’s most beautiful lagoons surrounding the South Pacific island of Aitutaki, Manureva Aquafest is the Cook Island Kitesurfing Association’s annual international event and is also recognised as one of the “Top 3 Signature Events” in the annual calendar forCook Islands Tourism.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/manureva/set-in-one-of-the-worlds-most-beautiful-lagoons-surrounding/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b65401cc-df54-4b19-bbcf-7350a864c167</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 06:37:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In memory of Tetuatau Leverd]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>In memory of Tetuatau Leverd</h1><p>In special honour of our 2014 Manureva Aquafest waterman of the year, this year’s event will be dedicated to the memory of legendary Tetuatau Leverd, who sadly passed away late last year. In recognition of his love for the ocean and contribution to watersports in the South Pacific, we will be joined by special guests including international pro ridersJesse Richman(two times Kitesurfing World Champion),Ewan Jaspan(Australia’s number one professional kitesurfer) and a group of Tahitian watermen and waterwomen who will lead Etau’s memorial service.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/manureva/in-memory-of-tetuatau-leverd/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4818a70d-3994-4f0d-91ac-b19ed5e44bef</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 06:37:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2016 International Guests ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>2016 International Guests </h1><h2>Jesse Richman </h2><p>Describing himself as “Two times Kitesurfing World Champion on a quest for any and every way to have fun through an intense adrenaline rush” few have dominated the sport (or nailed as many death-defying stunts) as Jesse during his decade long career as a professional athlete. Pro rider for Team Naish, 2013 Red Bull King of the Air and making kitesurfing history with the first successful kitesurfing barrel at Jaws, Maui; Jesse is always pushing the limits of extreme kitesurfing. He also ranks the Cook Islands as one of his favourite places to kite. We’re super excited to welcome Jesse back to Aitutaki again this year and look forward to his extreme, energetic kiting and fun sense of humour. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/12eca1cc-8ae7-4641-a5a3-c9ae7101b693.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://manureva-aquafest.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9d028bf9-6375-47d3-b4c8-7dac9e438afd</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 06:37:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>